

SANIDHYA JIWANAPURKAR

UI/UX DESIGNER

PROFILE

I bring an engineering perspective with three year of experience in creative problem solving approach to create products and build that people love. Currently working on multiple projects and looking to extra out of the ordinary design into new fields with more user interactivity.

" Design is intelligence made visible "

WHY UI/UX?

Working in UI/UX is highly satisfying as I am building value to business as well as people lives, that makes me good problem solver with pinch of creative thoughts.

ABILITIES







Wireframing

Prototyping

UX







User Research

Logo Designing

Typography



Color Theory

CERTIFICATIONS



Completed a course named 'Design Thinking for user experience' which is undertaken by renowned institute "IIT Delhi" in 2023.



Successfully completed "Advance Fundamentals of UI/UX " course from Coursera.



Successfully completed UI/UX design course from Udemy.

CONNECT



sanidhyajiwan@gmail.com



https://www.linkedin.com/in/ sanidhya-jiwanapurkar-91369918b/



8999760668



PROJECTS



Interactive Business Playbook powered Digital (Current) Application Platform(Enterprise level project)



(2020 - 2021)

Inventory management system within POS application. Also worked on Parent project "Thankucash" which is a multi-merchant loyalty and cashback platform

Aura (2020)

Aura is a secure SAAS application which enables secure and controlled access to regulation complaints, structured document authoring for medical and scientific document



WORK EXPERIENCE

2021 - Present (May 2021 -)

UI/UX Designer (VAST)

Currently working at 'VAST', as ui/ux designer on their internal products as well as clients projects in the organization.

2020 - 2021 (Dec 2020 - May 2021)

Jr. UI/UX Designer (Halcyonminds)

Worked for 6 months in the organization and created an inventory management module for their existing project that is "Thankucash"

2020 - 2020

UI/UX Designer (Metacognition)

Worked from May 2020 to November 2020 in the organization on contract basis and completed the ui/ux design of their only product successfully.

2019 - 2019 (Jun 2019 - July 2019)

Intern at (Adnate IT LLP)

Worked as web designer on leave management system



EDUCATION

2016 - 2020

Bachelor's of engineering in Information Technology Nagpur University

2014 - 2016

12th from State board with 58%

2014

10th from State board with 88%



SOFTWARE SKILLS







Adobe XD

Figma









Adobe Illustrator